<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<openerp>
<data>
       <report 
            id="share_register.report_share_purchase_agreement"
            model="share.block"
            string="Share Purchase Agreement"
            report_type="qweb-pdf"
            name="share_register.share_purchase_agreement"
            file="share_register.share_purchase_agreement"
            attachment_use="True"
        />
        <record id="share_register.report_share_purchase_agreement" model="ir.actions.report.xml">
            <field name="paperformat_id" ref="report.paperformat_euro"/>
        </record>
        

<template id="share_purchase_agreement_document">
    <div class="header">
        <div class="row">
            <div class="col-xs-3">
<!--                <h1 style="font-size:large;">-->
<!--                Owner: <span  t-field="o.owner_id.name" />-->
<!--                </h1>-->
<!--
                <div t-field="o.owner_id.name" t-field-options='{"widget": "contact", "fields": ["address"], "no_marker": true}' />
-->
            </div>
            <div class="col-xs-2" style="float:center">
                <img t-if="o.company_id.logo" t-att-src="'data:image/png;base64,%s' % o.company_id.logo" style="max-height: 100px;"/>
            </div>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
            <div class="col-xs-2" style="float:right">
                Date: <span t-esc="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d')"/>
            </div>
        </div>

        
    </div>


         <div class="page">
             <div class="row">
             
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<p><strong>AGREEMENT</strong> for purchase of shares in <span t-field="o.company_id.name" />, BVI Company Registration. No …. a Company registered in British Virgin Islands.</p>
<p>The Company is authorised to issue and has issued 50,000 registered shares with no par value in three classes being 90 voting 
management shares (“Management Shares”), 10 voting participating management shares all held by held by Mr. Kjell Edwall and 49,900 
non-voting ordinary shares (“Ordinary Shares”). It is understood that each Ordinary Share acquired according to this agreement at 
all times shall represent 1/49,900 of the total number of Ordinary Shares.</p>

<p>This Agreement is made between <br/>
(1) <strong>The Seller:</strong> Mr Kjell Roland Edwall, (born 1940-04-16), 1 Rue des Genêts, MC 98000 Monte Carlo, Monaco, and <br/>
(2) <strong><span t-esc="o.company_id.name"/></strong> of Nerine Chambers, Road Town, Tortola, British Virgin Islands, and    <br/>
(3) <strong>The Buyer:</strong> <span t-esc="o.owner_id.title.name"/> <span t-esc="o.owner_id.name"/>, (born <span t-esc="o.owner_id.birth_date"/>), 
<span t-esc="o.owner_id.contact_address"/>, <span t-esc="o.owner_id.email"/></p>

<p>§1.	<strong>The Seller</strong> holds Ordinary Shares in <span t-field="o.company_id.name" /> and is intending to sell all or part of the shares as set out in Schedule 1 to this agreement (the “Shares”);</p>
<p>§2.	<strong>The Seller</strong> agrees to sell, free from any encumbrances including any interest or equity of any person (including any right to acquire, 
option or right of pre-emption) or any mortgage, charge (fixed or floating), pledge, option, lien, assignment, hypothecation, security interest, 
title retention or any other security agreement or arrangement which has the effect of creating security or payment priority), and the Buyer 
agrees to buy <span t-field="o.number_of_shares"/> Shares from the Seller for the price of totally <span t-field="o.purchase_price" 
t-field-options='{"widget": "monetary", "display_currency": "o.company_id.currency_id"}'/> (the “Purchase Price”).</p>
<p>§3.	<strong>The Buyer</strong> agrees to pay for the Shares by transferring the total Purchase Price to the Seller’s bank account: 
SE-Banken, Stockholm, Sweden, Acc. No 5201-00 685 72, Acc. holder: Mr  Kjell Edwall with address as above (the “Account”). 
The payment shall be made so as to be in the Account no later than 14 business 
days after the date of this agreement. For the purpose of this agreement a business day shall mean any day (other than a Saturday, 
Sunday or public holiday) when banks are open for business in the British Virgin Islands/Sweden. </p>
<p>§4.	<strong>The Buyer</strong> shall receive within (60) days after full payment has been credited to the Account a newly issued share 
certificate in <span t-field="o.company_id.name" /> for the share(s) purchased.</p>
<p>§5.	<strong><span t-field="o.company_id.name" /></strong>* agrees that on receipt of monies arising from its investments and those monies being distributable within the meaning of the BVI 
Business Companies Act, first to pay by way of dividend on the 10 voting participating management shares such amount so that the Seller can 
pay to the Buyer the Principal Amount (as referred to in the Schedule) or such proportion as is available for distribution; secondly to repay 
any costs arising and incurred by the Seller; and thirdly after making reserves for working capital if any, to pay distributable revenues by way of dividend amongst all ordinary participating shareholders.</p>
<p>§6.	If the Buyer does not fulfil his obligations, the Seller has the right to cancel this agreement without notice.</p>
<p>§7.	Each party shall pay its own costs and expenses in relation to the negotiation, preparation, execution and carrying into effect of this agreement.</p>
<p>§8. 	This agreement and the documents referred to or incorporated in it constitute the entire agreement between the parties relating to the subject matter of this agreement and supersede and extinguish any prior drafts, agreements, undertakings, representations, warranties and arrangements of any nature whatsoever, whether or not in writing, between the parties in relation to the subject matter of this agreement</p>
<p>§9.	This agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the British Virgin Islands</p>
<p>§10.	A dispute having arisen between the parties concerning this agreement, the parties hereby agree that the dispute shall be referred to and finally resolved by arbitration under the [LCIA] Rules.
<ul>
	<li>-The number of arbitrators shall be three.</li>
	<li>-The seat, or legal place, of arbitration shall be Stockholm in Sweden.</li>
	<li>-The language to be used in the arbitral proceedings shall be English.</li>
	<li>-The governing law of the contract shall be the laws of the British Virgin Islands.</li>
</ul>
</p>
<p>§11.	It is hereby acknowledged that the subject matter of this Agreement is confidential by nature and in the interests of the Company, the Buyer, the Seller and other shareholders in the Company, the Buyer shall keep confidential the investment aims and purposes of the underlying companies and all Confidential Information that comes to his knowledge or his possession and agrees not to disclose any Confidential Information unless forced to do so by law or at the request of regulatory bodies. Confidential Information shall include information of whatever nature relating to the Investment Purpose which is obtained either in writing or orally from or pursuant to discussions with the management or employees of the Company, or its subsidiaries or affiliates (together the "Company parties") as well as analyses, compilation, studies and other documents which contain or otherwise reflect or are generated from such information, but shall not include information which is already in the public domain.</p>
<p>§12.	Each of the provisions of this agreement is severable.  If any such provision is or becomes illegal, invalid or unenforceable in any respect under the law of any jurisdiction , the legality, validity or enforceability in that jurisdiction of the remaining provisions of this agreement shall not in any way be affected or impaired thereby.</p>
<p>§13.	This agreement may be executed in any number of counterparts (whether original or facsimile) and by the parties on different counterparts, but shall not be effective until each party has executed at least one counterpart. Each counterpart shall constitute an original of this agreement but all the counterparts shall together constitute one and the same agreement. </p>

<div align="center">
<br/>
<br/>
								<table>
									<tr><td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;"><span t-esc="o.owner_id.city"/> <span t-esc="o.date_purchased" /></td>
									<td style="min-width:50px;max-width:50px;"></td>
									<td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;"><span t-esc="o.company_id.city"/> <span t-esc="o.date_purchased" /></td>
									<td style="min-width:50px;max-width:50px;"></td>
									<td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;"><span t-esc="o.company_id.city"/> <span t-esc="o.date_issued" /></td></tr>

									<tr><td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;"><br/>The Buyer: </td>
									<td style="min-width:50px;max-width:50px;"></td>
									<td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;"><br/>The Seller:</td></tr>
									<td style="min-width:50px;max-width:50px;"></td>
									<td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;"><br/><span t-field="o.company_id.name" />:</td>

									<tr><td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;"><br/><br/><hr/> </td>
									<td style="min-width:50px;max-width:50px;"></td>
									<td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;"><br/><br/><hr/></td>
									<td style="min-width:50px;max-width:50px;"></td>
									<td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;"><br/><br/><hr/></td></tr>
									

									<tr><td><span t-esc="o.owner_id.name"/> </td>
									<td style="min-width:50px;max-width:50px;"></td>
									<td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;">Kjell Edwall</td></tr>									
									<td style="min-width:50px;max-width:50px;"></td>
									<td style="min-width:300px;max-width:300px;">Director</td>
									

								</table>    
</div>			

<!--New page-->
<div>
								<span>
page-break{
    page-break-after:always;
    clear:both;
    display:block;
    }
								<h1 class="page-break">Schedule 1</h1>

								<br/>
Details of Ordinary Shares to be sold<br/>
Number of shares in <span t-field="o.company_id.name" /><br/>
Certificate No. <span t-field="o.name"/><br/>
Principal Amount: <span t-field="o.purchase_price"/> SEK
</span>                                
</div>
                                    
             </div>                       
        </div>

       <div class="footer">
          <div class="row">
            <div class="col-xs-12" style="float:center">
				<!--                Date: <span t-esc="time.strftime('%Y-%m-%d')"/>-->

<br/>
<br/>
			<div class="col-xs-12" align="center">
				<hr/>
				<span t-field="o.company_id.name" />, <span t-field="o.company_id.street" />, <t t-if="o.company_id.street2"><span t-field="o.company_id.street2" />, </t><span t-field="o.company_id.zip" /> <span t-field="o.company_id.city" />, <span t-field="o.company_id.country_id.name" />. <span t-field="o.company_id.website" /> <span t-field="o.company_id.email" />
			</div>
           </div>
        </div>
      </div>

</template>

<template id="share_purchase_agreement">
            <t t-call="report.html_container">
                <t t-foreach="doc_ids" t-as="doc_id" >
                    <t t-raw="translate_doc(doc_id, doc_model, 'owner_id.lang', 'share_register.share_purchase_agreement_document')" />                    
<!--                    <t t-call="share_register.share_purchase_agreement_document" />                    -->
                </t>
            </t>
        </template>
</data>
</openerp>
